A one man cop shop in a two-timing town
Family of Cops is a action, crime, tv movie film directed by Ted Kotcheff.
Paul Fein is a veteran police detective whose son Eddie is also a cop.
Paul is assigned to investigate the murder of a prominent businessman, and he soon learns that the field of suspects has
been narrowed down to two—the victim's sexually freewheeling wife Anna, and Paul's wild-child daughter Jackie.
Neither Paul nor Eddie believe that Jackie could have committed the murder, and soon Paul is using himself as a
decoy in a bid to find out more about what Anna does and doesn't know about her husband's death.
Paul Fein, played by Charles Bronson.
Jackie Fein, played by Angela Featherstone.
Eddie Fein, played by Sebastian Spence.
Mrs. Novacek #1, played by Kate Trotter.
Celia Brent, played by Caroline Barclay.
Adam Novacek, played by Simon MacCorkindale.
Family of Cops is a 1995 American-Canadian made-for-television crime drama film from Trimark Pictures, directed by
Ted Kotcheff and starring Charles Bronson, Daniel Baldwin, Angela Featherstone, and Sebastian Spence.
The film premiered on CBS on November 26, 1995.
It was filmed in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, United
States and Toronto, Ontario, Canada.
It is the first installment in the Family of Cops film series, and was followed by
Breach of Faith: A Family of Cops 2 (1997) and Family of Cops 3 (1999).
The film explores themes of police, hitman, cop, murder, gunfight.